{
    "subject": "resource/Frederick_Valentine_Melsheimer",
    "predicate": "property/wordnet_type",
    "object": "http://www.w3.org/2006/03/wn/wn20/instances/synset-scientist-noun-1",
    "human_readable": "Frederick Valentine Melsheimer is a scientist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9532117247581482,
            "question": "Is Frederick Valentine Melsheimer involved in research?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9320206642150879,
            "question": "What is Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.818711519241333,
            "question": "Are there any notable discoveries or contributions associated with Frederick Valentine Melsheimer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8118124008178711,
            "question": "Has Frederick Valentine Melsheimer published any scientific papers or books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7331601977348328,
            "question": "What field of study does Frederick Valentine Melsheimer likely specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6506820321083069,
            "question": "Can you find any examples of Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's research projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5427902936935425,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4641975164413452,
            "question": "Are there any awards or recognitions received by Frederick Valentine Melsheimer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43465766310691833,
            "question": "What is the impact of Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's work on his field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41125696897506714,
            "question": "What universities or institutions might Frederick Valentine Melsheimer be affiliated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederick Valentine Melsheimer is a scientist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5227_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the impact of Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's work on his field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5227_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any awards or recognitions received by Frederick Valentine Melsheimer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5227_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5227_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5227_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all four documents mention Frederick Valentine Melsheimer, and in document 13.txt, it is explicitly stated that he was \"an influential American entomologist and Lutheran minister\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer being an influential American entomologist and one of the earliest American entomologists. This supports his status as a scientist, particularly in the field of entomology."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}